https://www.bricksrus.com/privacy-policy/

Blog
BRICK CAMPAIGNS MADE EASY!
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.
To better protect your privacy, we are providing this notice explaining our online information practices.
We have a variety of security measures in place to maintain the safety of your personal information.  The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected in these pages include name, company name, address, email address, telephone number, cellular number and fax number.
If you provide information when placing an order, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request for our products.  If you provide your information when requesting additional information from us or when accessing our www.bricksrus.com website, we will use this information only in our effort to supply you with the requested content and to improve your online shopping experience with us.
Our Online Ordering System is a secure site for the protection of our customers.  Bricks R Us only uses the inscription information entered to fulfill our customer’s orders.  Any donor information entered is for the sole purpose of our customers and we do not use that information in any other capacity.
Bricks R Us does not sell the information that you provide.  Information is used solely for the purposes outlined above.  We will only disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena.
If you have any questions or concerns about the Bricks R Us Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at privacy@bricksrus.com and we will be happy to speak with you.
Copyright © 2020 Bricks R Us. All Rights Reserved.
|  Privacy Policy
Have Questions?
Chat Live Now!
